
[
    {
      "question": "매우",
      "answer": "very (formal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "아주",
      "answer": "very (casual)"
    },
    {
      "question": "꽤",
      "answer": "quite"
    },
    {
      "question": "상당히",
      "answer": "quite"
    },
    {
      "question": "거의",
      "answer": "almost"
    },
    {
      "question": "빨리",
      "answer": "fast"
    },
    {
      "question": "천천히",
      "answer": "slowly"
    },
    {
      "question": "신중하게",
      "answer": "carefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "항상",
      "answer": "always (formal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "늘",
      "answer": "always (casual)"
    },
    {
      "question": "자주",
      "answer": "frequently (regularly)"
    },
    {
      "question": "흔히",
      "answer": "frequently (common occurrence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "보통",
      "answer": "usually"
    },
    {
      "question": "가끔",
      "answer": "sometimes (occasionally, not often)"
    },
    {
      "question": "때로는",
      "answer": "sometimes (on certain occasions)"
    },
    {
      "question": "좀처럼",
      "answer": "seldom"
    },
    {
      "question": "드물게",
      "answer": "rarely"
    },
    {
      "question": "결코",
      "answer": "never (formal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "절대",
      "answer": "never (casual)"
    }
  ]
  